Finding Aid for Stephen M. Ross School of Business (University of Michigan) records, 1916-2017
Bentley Historical Library
- Audiovisual Material, 1926-2014; undated
  - Photographs, 1926-1985
    - Alumni
      - Events
        - 1999 (Box 144)
        - 2001 (Box 144)
        - 1996-2000 (Box 144)
      - Alumni Photographs, 2002 (Box 144)
      - CD Yearbook, 2003
      - UMBS 2001: A B-School Odyssey
      - Homecoming, 2002
      - Alumni Weekend, 0001, 2002
      - Alumni Weekend, 0003, 2002
    - Misc Digital Photographs
      - BBSA, 2005
      - Commencement, 2013
      - Commencement, 2013
      - Commencement, 2006
      - Alison Davis-Blake + others, 2 of 2, 2013
      - Alison Davis-Blake + others, 1 of 2, 2013
      - Ross Art Collection, undated
      - Dean Dolan Farewell Pictures, 2011
      - RSB Evening MBAs Commerce Park Campus, 2006
      - Women's Leadership Council, 2003
      - RSB Archive Photos, 2005
      - Integrated Product Development TMI, undated
      - MAP, 2006
      - BSB High School Program, undated
      - BBSA, undated
      - Section 6 Pictures, 2003
      - Photo of Dean Dolan, 2002
      - Class Gift Photo, 2002
      - Student Lounge, undated
      - Commencement, 2004
      - Commencement Photos, 2003
      - Commencement Photos, 2003
      - Alumni Weekend, 002, 2002
      - Investors Brochure Image, undated
      - PhD Program Scans, 2005
      - Office of Communications, 2005
      - Office of Communications, undated
      - BBSA, 2005
  - Slides, 1950s-1990
    The Slides series (3 folders and one binder) contains the slides and script for a slide presentation about the school's Kalmbach Management Center, which was produced in 1977. There are also scenes of the school's facilities which date from the 1950s, promotional material from the Executive Development Program during the 1980s.
    - Executive Development Program, circa 1980s (Box 105)
    - Kalmbach Management Center, circa late 1970s (Box 105)
    - Kalmbach Management Center slide presentation, with script, 1977 (Box 105)
    - School of Business Administration scenes, circa 1950s (Box 105)
    - BBA Lunch, 1990 (Box 115)
    - Board Room (Box 115)
    - Computing Center (Box 115)
    - Commencement, 1989-1990 (Box 115)
    - Dean's Reception, 1987 (Box 115)
    - Interior and Exterior of Business School Buildings (Box 115)
    - Faculty and Staff, identified, 11 folders (Box 115)
    - Michigan Media (Box 115)
    - Slideshow and notes, 1980 (Box 115)
    - Students, identified, 5 folders (Box 115)
    - Unidentified students and staff, 1988-1990; 2 folders (Box 115)
    - Collected Slides
      - Misc. Slides, undated (Box 138)
      - Slide Binder #1, undated (Box 138)
      - Slide Binder #2, undated (Box 139)
      - Slide Binder #3, undated (Box 139)
      - Slide Binder #4, undated (Box 139)
      - Slide Binder #5, undated (Box 139)
      - Slides A-F (Box 140)
      - Slides G-Z (Box 140)
    - Reunion, 2001 (Box 143)
    - Alumni Golf Outing, 1999 (Box 143)
    - Student and Event Slides, undated (Box 140)
  - Dividend Magazine Photos, 1935; 1969-1989
    The Dividend Magazine series is divided into two subseries: Negatives and Proofs, and Photographs. The two subseries have some overlap in the material they contain, but each includes some unique material as well. The majority of the material in the Negatives and Proofs subseries is from 1973-1978, and documents student life, faculty, classroom activities, various lecture series, Dean Bond, and the construction of Paton Accounting Center. There is also some material documenting women and African Americans at the school, as well as Gerald Ford's visit to the school in 1977.
    The Photographs subseries contains material primarily from 1977 to 1989. In addition to documenting many of the same types of people and activities as the negatives and proofs do, the photographs also show the construction of the Business Administration Library and some of the activities of Dean Whitaker.
    - Negatives and Proofs
      - Class Picture, 1935 (Box 107)
      - Pre, 1973
        - Code Word "AIESEC" (Winter 1970) (Box 107)
        - General Shots of Bus. Ad. School and Students, January, 1970; 2 folders (Box 107)
        - Faculty Newcomers, 1970 (Box 107)
        - Business Administration Assembly Hall-Architect's Plans, 1970 (Box 107)
        - Honors Banquet, 1971 (Box 107)
        - Admin. Conference in Detroit (Box 107)
        - Institute for Businessmen-Detroit (Box 107)
        - Classroom Pictures (Box 107)
        - Code Word "Computer" (Box 107)
        - Paul McCracken (Box 107)
        - Night School, 2 folders (Box 107)
        - Visiting Committee (Decade of Publication) (Box 107)
        - Code Word "Arthur Young" (Box 107)
        - School of Business Administration (Box 107)
        - Student Activity Posters (Box 107)
      - 1974
        - Architectural Details of Buildings on Campus (Winter 1978) (Box 107)
        - New Faculty, 2 folders (Box 107)
      - 1975
        - Actuary in Residence (Box 107)
        - Candid Shots-Dean Bond (Box 107)
        - Annual Business Conference (Box 107)
        - Dayton-Hudson Seigel-Macy Lecture (Box 107)
        - Village Plaza Dearborn (Box 107)
        - New Faculty Dinner (Box 107)
        - Presentation, Dr. Frank Moore (Box 107)
        - Paton Center Groundbreaking (Box 107)
        - Board Meeting-Paton Center (Box 107)
        - Paton Center Construction (Box 107)
        - Student Presentation (Box 107)
        - Teaching (Box 107)
        - Visiting Committee (Winter 1976) (Box 107)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 107)
      - 1976
        - Brothers in School (Spring 1976) (Box 107)
        - Bus. Ad. Graduation (Spring 1976) (Box 107)
        - Business Leadership Award (Spring 1976) (Box 107)
        - 50th Class Reunion, Winter and Fall 1976 (Box 107)
        - Dean's Reception, 2 folders (Box 107)
        - Alice Greco (Box 107)
        - Green Thumb, Winter 1977; 2 folders (Box 107)
        - ITT Lecture Series (Box 107)
        - Kapnick Luncheon-League (Box 107)
        - Paton Center (Box 107)
        - Paton Center Dedication (Box 107)
        - Paton Interiors (Box 107)
        - Ph.D. Award (Spring 1976) (Box 107)
        - Ph.D. Committee (Box 107)
        - Values Lecture (Spring 1976) (Box 107)
      - 1977
        - Computer Room (Fall 1977) (Box 107)
        - Coopers and Lybrand-Campus Inn (Box 107)
        - Coopers and Lybrand-Frank Hennessey (Box 107)
        - Dean's Reception and Dean's Dinner (Box 107)
        - Our Athletic Faculty, Winter 1978; 2 folders (Box 107)
        - Ford Visit (Winter 1978) (Box 107)
        - Pictures for Ric Johnson (Box 107)
        - Fleming and Hildebrand, Bond and Heineman (Box 107)
        - IBM Vice President (Winter 1978) (Box 107)
        - First ITT Lecture, March, 1977 (Box 107)
        - Second ITT Lecture, March, 1977 (Box 107)
        - Third ITT Lecture, March, 1977 (Box 107)
        - MBAs (Fall 1977) (Box 107)
        - MacInally Lecture (Box 107)
        - Ph.D. Women (Spring 1977), Our Athletic Faculty (Winter 1978), Real World Teaching (Spring 1977), Minority Businessman (Fall 1977) (Box 107)
        - Plaque-Very Large Databases (Box 107)
        - Real World Dis. (Spring 1977) (Box 107)
        - Hessy (Bus. Ad. Buildings) (Box 107)
        - Bus. Leadership Award (Box 107)
      - 1978
        - BBA Students (Spring 1979) (Box 108)
        - Black Business Students (Box 108)
        - Bus. Ad. Graduation (Spring 1978) (Box 108)
        - Business Leadership Award (Box 108)
        - Cornish and Bond (Box 108)
        - New Dean, BBA Students (Box 108)
        - Dean's Reception and Dinner (Fall 1978) (Box 108)
        - Dean Bond's Recognition Dinner (Winter 1979) (Box 108)
        - Ford Scholars (Spring 1979) (Box 108)
        - Goodrich President (Box 108)
        - International Students (Spring 1978) (Box 108)
        - Kroger Chairman (Winter 1979) (Box 108)
        - MacInally Lecture (Spring 1978) (Box 108)
        - Mid-West Deans' Conference (Box 108)
        - BBA Students and Paton Center Director (Spring 1979) (Box 108)
        - Round Table-Inflation (Winter 1979) (Box 108)
        - Office Artifacts (Box 108)
        - Students-Mother and Daughter, Father and Daughter (Winter 1979) (Box 108)
        - Visiting Committee (Winter 1979) (Box 108)
      - 1979
        - Summer Jobs (Fall 1979) (Box 108)
        - Black Business Students' Lunch (Fall 1979) (Box 108)
      - circa 1979-1989
        - James A. Henderson, President, Cummins Engine Company, Winter 1980 (Box 108)
        - Winter 1981 (Box 108)
        - Phonathon, Spring 1983 (Box 108)
        - Paton's Book, Spring 1984 (Box 108)
        - Jim Sitlington, Intern at the Mercantile Exchange, April 1986 (Box 108)
        - Spring 1987 (Box 108)
        - "Tree Spirit" Sculpture, Winter 1989 (Box 108)
        - Minority High School Students, Winter 1989 (Box 108)
        - Homeless Auction, Spring 1989 (Box 108)
        - 1989-Berg Dinner, Fall 1989 (Box 108)
    - Photographs
      - Pre 1973 (Box 108)
        - Larry Taylor's Winter Issue Pictures, 1969 (Box 108)
        - Winter 1970 (Box 108)
        - Unused pictures (Winter 1970) (Box 108)
        - Faculty Newcomers, 1970 (Box 108)
        - Business Administration Assembly Hall-Architect's Plans, 1970 (Box 108)
        - Honors Banquet, 1971 (Box 108)
        - Institute for Businessmen-Detroit (Box 108)
        - Paul McCracken (Box 108)
        - Night School (Box 108)
        - Visiting Committee (Decade of Publication) (Box 108)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 108)
      - Winter 1976 (Box 108)
      - Spring 1976 (Box 108)
        (Values)
      - 1976-Dean's Reception (Box 108)
      - Fall 1976, 2 folders (Box 108)
      - Fall 1976-50th Class Reunion, Winter 1976 (Box 108)
      - Winter 1977 (Box 108)
        (Greening of the Business School)
      - Spring 1977 (Box 108)
      - 1977
        - Hessy (Bus. Ad. Building) (Box 108)
        - Dean's Reception and Dean's Dinner (Box 108)
        - ITT Lecture (March 1977) (Box 108)
      - Fall 1977 (Box 108)
      - Winter 1978 (Box 108)
        (includes pictures of Ford Visit)
      - Spring 1978 (Box 108)
      - Fall 1978 (Box 108)
      - Winter 1979 (Box 108)
      - Spring 1979 (Box 108)
      - 1979-Summer Jobs (Fall 1979) (Box 108)
      - Fall 1979 (Box 108)
      - Winter 1980 (Box 108)
      - Spring 1980 (Box 108)
      - Update 1980 Update, 1981, 1980-1981 (Box 108)
      - Fall 1980 (Box 108)
      - Winter 1981 (Box 108)
      - Spring 1981 (Box 108)
      - 1981-Student Pledge Meeting (Box 108)
      - Update, 1981 (Box 108)
      - Fall 1981 (Box 108)
      - Winter 1982 (Box 108)
      - Spring 1982 (Box 108)
      - Update, 1982 (Box 108)
      - Fall 1982 (Box 108)
      - 1982
        - Groundbreaking-Library, 2 folders (Box 108)
        - Allen Merten-Computer Conf. (Box 108)
        - Venture Capital (Winter 1983) (Box 108)
      - 1982-1983-Business Administration Library Construction, October 25, 1982-November 22, 1983 (Box 108)
      - Winter 1983 (Box 108)
      - Spring 1983, 2 folders (Box 109)
      - Update 1983-Report of the Graduate School of Business Administration, The University of Michigan, July 1982-June, 1983 (Box 109)
      - Fall 1983 (Box 109)
      - 1983-Strategy Seminar (Winter 1984) (Box 109)
      - Winter 1984 (Box 109)
      - Spring 1984 (Box 109)
      - Fall 1984 (Box 109)
      - October 1984-Exec. in Residence (Fall 1984) (Box 109)
      - January 1985 (Box 109)
      - April 1985 (Box 109)
      - Spring 1985 (Box 109)
      - April 1986
        - Alumni Weekend and Miscellaneous (Box 109)
        - Summer Interns (Box 109)
      - 1986-Alumni Board of Govs., May 10, 1986 (Box 109)
      - September 1986 (Box 109)
      - circa 1986
        - Alumni Weekend (February 1987) (Box 109)
        - Student Speak Off (February 1987) (Box 109)
      - February 1987, 2 folders (Box 109)
      - Annual Report, 1987; 2 folders (Box 109)
      - Spring 1987 (Box 109)
      - Ca. 1987-Consortium (Spring 1987) (Box 109)
      - Fall 1987 (Box 109)
      - 1987-Ira Harris (Fall 1987) (Box 109)
      - Winter 1988, 2 folders (Box 109)
      - Spring 1988 (Box 109)
      - Annual Report, 1988; 2 folders (Box 109)
      - 1988-Real Estate Forum (Winter 1989) (Box 109)
      - circa 1988
        - Forum on Third World Debt (Spring 1988) (Box 109)
        - New Faculty (Winter 1989) (Box 109)
      - Winter 1989, 2 folders (Box 109)
      - Spring 1989-10 Great Years, 2 folders (Box 109)
      - Annual Report, 1989; 2 folders (Box 109)
      - Fall 1989, 3 folders (Box 109)
      - 1989
        - Pictures at Paton's Party (Fall 1989) (Box 109)
        - Follies (Fall 1989) (Box 109)
        - Pryor Award (Fall 1989) (Box 109)
      - Winter 1990, 3 folders (Box 110)
      - Spring 1990, 3 folders (Box 110)
      - Brussels, Belgium Conference, June 1990 (Box 110)
      - Fall 1990 (Box 110)
      - C. Procter and Gamble in Po, 1990 (Box 110)
      - Winter 1991 (Box 110)
      - Spring 1991, 2 folders (Box 110)
      - Fall 1991, 2 folders (Box 110)
      - Annual Report, 1991 (Box 110)
      - Mitsui Life Financial Research Center, 1991 (Box 110)
      - Real Estate Forum, 1991 (Box 110)
      - Student Trip to Russia, 1991 (Box 110)
      - Winter 1992, 3 folders (Box 110)
      - Spring/Summer 1992, 2 folders (Box 111)
      - Fall 1992, 3 folders (Box 111)
      - Highlights, 1992 (Box 111)
      - Library Groundbreaking and Construction, 1992 (Box 111)
      - Winter 1993, 3 folders (Box 111)
      - Spring 1993, 3 folders (Box 111)
      - Fall 1993, 4 folders (Box 111)
      - Alumni Reunion, 1993 (Box 111)
      - Highlights, 1993; 2 folders (Box 111)
      - Winter 1994, 3 folders (Box 111)
      - Spring/Summer 1994, 2 folders (Box 111)
      - Fall 1994, 2 folders (Box 112)
      - Joint Manufacturing Initiative, Dodge Truck Assembly (June 6), 1994 (Box 112)
      - C. Paul Danos, 1995 (Box 112)
      - Alumni Reunion, 1996 (Box 112)
      - Global Blue Video Shots, 1996 (Box 112)
      - Class of 1952 Emeritus Luncheon, 2002 (Box 112)
      - Dividend Photos, undated (Box 138)
  - Drawings, 1978
    - Line drawings of the Business School Exterior, 1978 (Box 114)
  - Microfilm, 1947
    A reel of microfilm records the contents of the Business Administration Building cornerstone, which was put in place at a dedication ceremony in 1947. The contents of the stone include photographs of students and facilities, floor plans of the new building, and copies of Business School publications.
    - Film of documents and other items placed in cornerstone, 1947 (Reel 1)
  - Sound Recordings, 1969-2005
    Tape recordings, on cassettes and reel-to-reel tape, include speeches by business leadership award winners and seminars run by faculty, dating from the late 1960s to the mid-1980s. There are also "State of the School" addresses given by Dean Bond during the 1970s.
    - Business Seminar led by Professors Crawford, Spivey and Terpstra, 1969; 2 reels (7-inch) (Box 95)
    - "Managing Change-No Magic Formula", speech by Business Leadership Award recipient Bernard M. Fauber, 1986; 1 audiocassettes (Box 95)
    - Mass Mutual Introduction to Kalmbach Management Center, circa 1977; 1 reels (7-inch) (Box 95)
    - Needham, J.J., on International Business, 1971; 1 reels (7-inch) (Box 95)
    - "Reaganomics" lecture by Dr. Murray Wiedenbaum, 1984; 1 audiocassettes (Box 95)
    - "Society's Challenge to Business", lecture by J. Philip Wernette, 1971; 1 reels (5-inch) (Box 95)
    - Stans, Maurice, Secretary of Commerce at Regional Business Administration Conference, 1969; 1 reels (5-inch) (Box 95)
    - State of the School Address, 1973-1974; 2 audiocassettes (Box 95)
    - Townsend, Lynn, of Chrysler Corp. at Regional Business Administration Conference, 1969 November 12; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 5 inch (Box 95)
      [Digitized audio files are only available in the Bentley Historical Library reading room on designated Bentley Library computers.]
      - [Part 1], [87296-SR-1-1]; (Lynn Townsend, President of Chrysler Corporation at the Regional Business Administration Conference: Economic Prognosis for the US and the Automobile Industry.)
    - [Boxes 96-99 were eliminated during 1994 reprocessing.] (Box 96)
    - [Boxes 96-99 were eliminated during 1994 reprocessing.] (Box 97)
    - [Boxes 96-99 were eliminated during 1994 reprocessing.] (Box 98)
    - [Boxes 96-99 were eliminated during 1994 reprocessing.] (Box 99)
    - Bill Poorman Audio, 2003
    - Business School Raw Tapes, undated
    - Kim Cameron Bookends Interivew, undated
    - Jack Walker Audio Tracks, undated
    - RSB Testimony, undated
    - CK Prahalad Audio Files, undated
    - U of M Business School Testimonial Radio, 2000
    - Interview Clips, 2005
    - Interview w/Linda Pulwecki, 2003
  - Moving Image Recordings, 1988-2014
    The Moving Image Recordings series contains videocassettes and digital files of Ross School of Business student life, faculty lectures, promotional materials, events and development materials.
    - Student Life
      - Follies
        - 1988-1989, 1 videocassettes (VHS) (Box 128)
        - 1992-1995, 1 videocassettes (VHS) (Box 128)
        - 1997-1998, 1 videocassettes (VHS) (Box 128)
        - 2000, 1 videocassettes (VHS) (Box 128)
        - 2001, 1 videocassettes (VHS) (Box 128)
        - 2003, 1 videocassettes (VHS) (Box 128)
        - Assorted Follies: Feel the Love, 2003
      - Life at the B-School, undated; 1 videocassettes (VHS) (Box 128)
    - Meeting of the Combined Advisory Boards
      - "Cracking the Code of Life", 2002; 1 videocassettes (VHS) (Box 128)
      - "The Secret of Our Lives", 2002; 1 videocassettes (VHS) (Box 128)
    - Conferences
      - Leadership Development Program, undated; 1 videocassettes (VHS) (Box 128)
      - Leadership Convocation: "The Passion of a Volunteer", 2002; 1 videocassettes (VHS) (Box 128)
      - Leaders Connect: A Company of Leaders, 2002; 1 videocassettes (VHS) (Box 128)
      - Leaders Connect: Strategic Interviewing, 2002; 1 videocassettes (Box 128)
    - Alumni
      - Reunion 2002: Annual Business Conference, 1 videocassettes (VHS) (Box 128)
      - Class of 1974, 25th Reunion, 2001; 1 videocassettes (VHS) (Box 128)
    - Development
      - "Risky Business": Michigan Business School Kick-Off Campaign, 1992; 1 videocassettes (VHS) (Box 128)
      - Announcement of Stephen Ross gift to business school (1 of 2), 2004; 1 videocassettes (Betacamp-SP) (Box 128)
      - Announcement of Stephen Ross gift to business school (2 of 2), 2004; 1 videocassettes (Betacam-SP) (Box 128)
    - Graduations
      - M.B.A. class of 1996, 1 videocassettes (VHS) (Box 95)
      - Class of 1996, 1 videocassettes (VHS) (Box 128)
      - Class of 1997, 1 videocassettes (VHS) (Box 128)
      - Global Blue Graduation Rally, 1998; 1 videotape (VHS) (Box 128)
      - Class of 1998, 1 videocassettes (VHS) (Box 128)
      - Graduation Rally, 2002; 1 videocassettes (VHS) (Box 128)
    - POS Participant Interviews, 2008
    - Groundbreaking Celebration, 2006
    - C.K. Prahalad: Unedited Interview for Executive Forum, 2004
    - Your Michigan Advantage!, undated
    - The Power of Positive Leadership, undated
    - Jack Walker: Executive Education Program Preview, undated
    - Beer Game, Distribution Game, undated
    - Commencement, 2014
    - Michigan Difference Campaign Thank You, undated
    - Admissions Presentation Video Clips, 2004
    - The Campaign for Michigan, undated
    - BBA Celebration Alumni Address: Jeff Blau, 2009
    - Producing Leaders, 2001
    - Global Blue Rendevous clips, 2006
    - Henry Carter Adams Society, undated
    - 2008 Campaign Thank You
    - John Monoky Sales Management Video, 2005
    - The William Davidson Institute: Globalization Project, undated
    - Leading Change, 2005
    - Leadership Conference, Ann Arbor, undated
    - Admissions Clips, 2006
    - Dean Doland NYSE Closing Bell, 2002
    - A Conversation with Jack Welch, 2005
    - Schematic Design Kick Off, 2005
    - Senator Carl Levin: Speech on Climate Change, 2005
    - Ross Announcement Highlights DVD, undated
    - Ross Donation To U of M School: National Coverage, 2004
    - Indian Video, undated
    - India Alumni Association, 2003
    - Class of 1996 Video, 2006
    - Class of 2000 Graduation Slideshows
  - Oversize Photographs and Awards, 1984; undated
    The Oversized Photographs and Awards series contains 16 oversized Business School Leadership awards and a poster regarding the dedications of the Kresge Library and proposed plans for expansion of the school.
    - Proposed Projects for Graduate School of Business Administration (Box 145)
    - Kresge Library Dedication, 1984 (Box 145)
    - Awards (Box 145)
    - Awards (Box 145)
    - Awards (Box 145)
  - Oversize Posters, 2003
    - Kresge Library Open House, 2003; 1 oversize folder (Posters) (Folder 1)
- Architectural Records, 1943-1998
  The Architectural Records subgroup (1 linear foot and 3 oversize folders) contains design records for School of Business buildings including the Kresge Business Library, the Paton Accounting Center, and a 1998 Campus Plan Phase 1 Overview.
  - Kresge Business Library, 1995
    - Computer Center, January 20, 1995; undated; 1 oversize folder (Folder 2)
    - Business and Finance Electronic Library, January 25, 1995; 1 oversize folder (Folder 3)
  - School of Business Administration Building, 1944-1974
    The Architectural Records subgroup is divided into three series: School of Business Administration, Paton Accounting Center, and Topical Files. The School of Business Administration series contains floor plans and other architectural drawings of the original School of Business Administration building. The Paton Accounting Center series also includes floor plans from the created before and during of the Center in the 1970s. The Topical Files series contains larger views of planned expansion of the campus in 1943 and the School of Business Administration in the 1970s. It also includes plans for the Kalmbach Management Center, the Business Administration Assembly Hall, and the school's landscaping in the 1970s.
    - Two Proposal Drawings, circa 1944 (Box 112)
    - Aerial Mass Study and First Floor Plan, August 23, 1944 (Box 112)
    - Floor Plans, September 20, 1944 (Box 112)
    - First Floor Plan, October 24, 1944 (Box 112)
    - Bureau of Industrial Relations, February 14, 1945 (Box 112)
    - Tower Plan and Spandrel Section (Types A and B), Tower Study, March 26, 1945 (Box 112)
    - Key Plan-Second Floor, January 22, 1946 (Box 112)
    - North, South, East, and West Elevations, February 21, 1946 (Box 112)
    - Plot Plan, March 8, 1946 (Box 112)
    - Floor Plans
      - Revised, June, 1958 (Box 112)
      - Revised, October, 1960 (Box 112)
      - circa 1964 (Box 112)
      - circa 1971 (Box 112)
      - Revised, January 21, 1974 (Box 112)
      - Revised, February 1, 1974 (Box 112)
    - Floor Plans for Remodeling Rooms for Placement Offices, March, 1967 (Box 112)
    - Women's Lounge, December, 1973 (Box 112)
  - Paton Accounting Center, 1973-1976
    - Floor Plans, October 10, 1973 (Box 112)
    - Plans, circa 1973 (Box 112)
    - Floor Plans, Revised, September 30, 1974 (Box 112)
    - Floor Plans, August 3, 1975 (Box 112)
    - Floor Plans, undated (Box 112)
    - Second Floor Offices, September, 1975 (Box 112)
    - Archives, Seminar, and Conference Rooms, Revised, November, 1975 (Box 112)
    - Publications Office, February, 1976 (Box 112)
  - Topical Files, 1943-1976; 1998
    - Proposed Development of the Campus of the University of Michigan, 1943 (Box 112)
    - Business Administration Site, circa 1970s (Box 112)
    - Kalmbach Management Center, September 13, 1972 (Box 112)